collegeessayguy.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy

_Last updated: 5/28/18_

###  **General**

College Essay Guy ("us", "we", or "our") operates the domain collegeessayguy.com and collects information on collegeessayguy.mykajabi.com and go.collegeessayguy.com. All of these domains will be referred to as the "Sites". This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information and other information we receive from users of the Sites. By using the Sites, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

###  **AGE RESTRICTION**

You cannot use the Sites if you are younger than 16 years old and have not gotten permission to use them from your parents or guardians. If you are using the Sites and you are under the age of 16, then you are promising that you have gotten this permission.

###  **INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

While using our Sites, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name, email address, address, payment information, zip codes, and specific demographic information like ethnicity, age, and job ("Personal Information"). We are the sole owners of the information collected on these Sites. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

Privacy and transparency are really important to us. That's why we created this detailed [Data Map](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1gnEkVVo1bLM8pSB3SRgTPhra8a_YpoX8D0fXwH1e9TE/edit#gid=0) of the kinds of information that we might collect on these Sites, how we'll collect it, the purposes we have for collecting this information, who has access to it, how long we'll keep it, and more. We may update this Data Map over time in order to keep it in line with our systems.

###  **Log Data**

Like many Site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Sites ("Log Data").

This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Sites that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor, and analyze this data in order to improve our services and products We may also contract with third party advertising services that collect, monitor, and analyze this data on Facebook in order to find and offer services to potential customers.

###  **Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, and other information that offers recommendations of our free and paid services and content.

###  **REGISTRATION**

In order to use some sections of these Sites, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our Sites in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.

###  **ORDERS**

We request information from you on our order form when you purchase video courses, guides, or services. To buy from us or lease our services, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.

###  **Surveys and contests**

From time-to-time our Sites or individuals with email addresses using domain the "collegeessayguy.com" will request information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this Site.

###  **Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Sites. You can see the kinds of cookies we use on our [Sites](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1gnEkVVo1bLM8pSB3SRgTPhra8a_YpoX8D0fXwH1e9TE/edit#gid=0) and what kinds of information they collect here.

###  **Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.

 **LINKS**

These Sites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Sites and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

###  **Your Access to and Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or contact form given on our [Sites](https://www.collegeessayguy.com/contact):

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
  * Security 

###  **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 5/28/18 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our Sites.

###  **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us as info@collegeessayguy.com.

##  **[Click here for THE Terms of Use for our Courses, products, and services](https://www.collegeessayguy.com/terms-of-use)**

##  **[Click here for THE TERMS OF USE FOR OUR WEBSITE](https://www.collegeessayguy.com/terms-of-use-website)**
